guitarprotabs.net 2019-08-07

# - Guitar Pro Tab

## Privacy Policy

GuitarProTabs.net is committed to protecting your privacy. GuitarProTabs.net does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. GuitarProTabs.net will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by GuitarProTabs.net. At some point GuitarProTabs.net may share information with selected partners who work with us to deliver services. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, GuitarProTabs.net may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information. 

Newsletter Anti-Spam Policy tolerates only permission-based email. In addition, users always have the opportunity to opt-out or change preferences via a link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages. These options are made available when you sign-up for our email lists and in email messages delivered from our company. Alternatively, you may email us. If you believe that you have received an unsolicited commercial email from Newsletter on behalf of any of our customers, you may report it to us. 

### Modification of Privacy Policy

GuitarProTabs.net reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
